Inventory of the Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills records 1872-1994 MS004
Archives & Records Management, Library and Information Center, Georgia Institute of Technology
- Strike records, 1897-1919 (bulk 1914-1915).; SERIES 2; 4.9 linear feet (7 document cases and Oversize)
  - Subject files, 1897-1919 (bulk 1914).; SERIES 2, Subseries 1; 1.0 Linear feet; (3 document cases)
    - Commission on Industrial Relations (folder 1 of 4), 1915; undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Notes on witnesses, ca. 1915; MS004-062
      - "Report from Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, Atlanta GA", ca. 1915; MS004-063
    - Commission on Industrial Relations (folder 2 of 4), 1915; undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Summons for Oscar Elsas to appear before the Commission on Industrial Relations, March 15, 1915; MS004-064
      - "The Mote in Your Neighbor's Eyes, the Beam in Your Own", ca. 1915; MS004-065
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Richard Sloss, March 18, 1915; MS004-066
    - Commission on Industrial Relations (folder 3 of 4), 1915; undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Industrial Relations (folder 4 of 4), 1915; undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - "Anarchism!", April 8, 1915; MS004-067
    - Commissioners of Conciliations, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Confidential circulars, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Detective agencies, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Letter from J. H. Kelley, Pinkerton's National Detective Agency to Gordon A. Johnstone, August 28, 1914; MS004-041
    - Housing, 1910-1914 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Jamison, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Jamison, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - McDavid and Preston, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Men and Religion Forward movement (folder 1 of 2), 1914 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - "Meeting at Grand Theatre, Atlanta, Georgia under the Auspices of 'Men and Religion Forward Movement'", June 28, 1914; MS004-042
    - Men and Religion Forward movement (folder 2 of 2), 1914 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Mullinax, Augusta, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Our forces (folder 1 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Operative notes, June 14, 1914; MS004-043
      - Operative notes from W. L. Shields, December 18, 1914; MS004-044
      - Operative notes, June 3, 1914; MS004-045
      - Operative notes, May 29, 1914; MS004-046
      - Operative notes, June 3, 1914; MS004-047
    - Our forces (folder 2 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Our forces (folder 3 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Our forces (folder 4 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Our forces (folder 5 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Our forces (folder 6 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Letter from R. K. McCuen to J. W. McCuen and Operative Notes, August 30, 1914; MS004-048
    - Our forces (folder 7 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Our forces (folder 8 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Notices Given June 8/14, June 8, 1914; MS004-050
    - Our forces (folder 9 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Our forces (folder 10 of 10), 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Operative notes, 1914; MS004-052
    - Press coverage: Men and Religion, union activity, 1914-1917 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Press coverage: Men and Religion, union activity, 1914-1917 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Record of employee fines (see OVERSIZE), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Record of employee fines (see OVERSIZE), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Skyland magazine, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Strike, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Strike (folder 1 of 2), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Strike (folder 2 of 2), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - "Workers of Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills Attention", ca. 1914; MS004-040
    - Strike participants, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Sworn statements (folder 1 of 2), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Statement of Lonnie Middlebrooks, May 22, 1914; MS004-032
      - Statement of Arthur Watson, May 26, 1914; MS004-033
      - Statement of Otis A. Thomason, May 25, 1914; MS004-0331
      - Statement of Charles Mathis, May 25, 1914; MS004-0332
    - Sworn statements (folder 2 of 2), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Threats, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Threat note to Mrs. Burdett, July 10, 1914; MS004-034
      - Threat note to Mrs. Hardman, July 10, 1914; MS004-035
      - "Statement by Melvin Manus", May 23, 1914; MS004-037
    - United Textile Workers (folder 1 of 4), 1914-1919 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - United Textile Workers (folder 2 of 4), 1914-1919 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - "Strike on Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills", ca. 1914; MS004-029
      - "Mass Meeting", ca. 1914; MS004-030
    - United Textile Workers (folder 3 of 4), 1914-1919 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - United Textile Workers (folder 4 of 4), 1914-1919 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - "Workers Attention", ca. 1914; MS004-031
    - Vaughan (police): Sworn statements, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1909-1918 (bulk 1914-1915).; SERIES 2, Subseries 2; 0.8 Linear feet; (2 document cases)
    Subseries 2 consists of the correspondence of Oscar Elsas, President of Fulton Bag during the period of the 1914-1915 strike. Elsas' correspondence illustrates his concerns about union activity among mill workers, police protection and patrolling of the mill village, operation of the mill during the strike, and preparation for the hearings before the U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations. His correspondents include police chief James L. Beavers, Congressman William Schley Howard, the management of other Fulton Bag mills, management in the Atlanta Fulton Bag mill and other area textile mills, lawyers, and former and current employees.
    This subseries is organized into two chronological groups of correspondence. The first group covers the years 1913-1915; the second group is a set of miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda dating from 1909 to 1918.
    - Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January 1914 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, May 1914 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 4), June 1914 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to the Southern Textile Bulletin, June 9, 1914; MS004-070
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to David Clark, Southern Textile Bulletin, June 22, 1914; MS004-071
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to the Southern Textile Bulletin, July 25, 1914; MS004-073
      - "Relations between Employers and Operatives", April 2, 1914; MS004-074
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to James L. Beavers, Chief of Police, Atlanta, June 4, 1914; MS004-075
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 4), June 1914 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (folder 3 of 4), June 1914 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (folder 4 of 4), June 1914 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 4), July 1914 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 4), July 1914 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Hoke Smith, U.S. Senate, July 9, 1914; MS004-079
    - Correspondence (folder 3 of 4), July 1914 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to the Congressional Information Bureau, September 21, 1914; MS004-080
      - "Strikers' Journal, Vol. 1, No. 1", July 18, 1914; MS004-083
    - Correspondence (folder 4 of 4), July 1914 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Letter from operative to Jacob Elsas, July 17, 1914; MS004-084
    - Correspondence, August 1914 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, September 1914 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - "House Resolution 621", September 15, 1914; MS004-085
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to William Schley Howard, U.S. House of Representatives, September 17, 1914; MS004-086
      - "Asks Investigation for Atlanta Strike", September 16, 1914; MS004-087
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 2), October 1914 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Thomas W. Hardwick, U.S. House of Representatives, October 3, 1914; MS004-088
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 2), October 1914 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, November 1914 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Letter from Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills to James L. Beavers, Chief of Police, Atlanta, November 25, 1914; MS004-089
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 2), December 1914 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Statement on strikes at the Fulton Bag and Cotton Mill in Altanta, Georgia, December 15, 1914; MS004-090
      - Article on the tent colony at the Fulton Bag and Cotton Mill in Atlanta, Georgia, ca. December 1914; MS004-091
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Arthur St. George Joyce, December 16, 1914; MS004-092
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 2), December 1914 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, January 1915 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Robert H. Wright, January 25, 1914; MS004-094
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 2), February 1915 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to James A. Emery, National Council for Industrial Defense, February 11, 1915; MS004-097
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Thomas W. Hardwick, U.S. House of Representatives, February 11, 1915; MS004-099
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 2), February 1915 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Headnotes for Jones et al. vs. Van Winkle Gin and Machine Works, ca. 1915; MS004-100
      - Letter from Roser, Brandon, Slaton, and Phillips to Oscar Elsas, February 26, 1915; MS004-101
    - Correspondence, March 1915 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Edwards-Adams Studio, March 27, 1915; MS004-103
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 2), April 1915 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 2), April 1915 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to F. A. Weiss, Wolston Manufacturing Company, April 23, 1915; MS004-106
    - Correspondence (folder 1 of 2), May 1915 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Letter from C. L. Denk to Oscar Elsas, May 2, 1915; MS004-107
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to John Y. Phillips, May 1, 1915; MS004-108
    - Correspondence (folder 2 of 2), May 1915 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to H. P. Meikleham, Massachusetts Mills in Georgia, May 14, 1915; MS004-110
    - Correspondence, June 1915 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Walter Drew, National Erectors' Association, June 30, 1915; MS004-111
    - Correspondence, July 1915 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Walter Drew, National Erectors' Association, July 7, 1915; MS004-112
    - Correspondence, September 1915 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, November 1915 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, December 1915 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1909-1914 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Article reports, general notes, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and petition (folder 1 of 2), 1914-1915 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Excerpt of a petition for police protection from strikers by employees of Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, ca. 1914; MS004-114
    - Correspondence and petition (folder 2 of 2), 1914-1915 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - "Strike Waged in Georgia Factory", August 15, 1914; MS004-116
      - "Memo of Discussion Held with Mr. McWade and Mr. Colpoys", November 27, 1914; MS004-117
      - Letter from Jacob Elsas to James R. Gray, The Atlanta Journal, August 7, 1914; MS004-118
    - Correspondence, (reports, articles), 1914-1919 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, special report: Jacob Elsas, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Letter from Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills to James S. Alexander, National Bank of Commerce, July 3, 1914; MS004-120
      - Letter from Louis J. Elsas to C. B. Wilmer, July 11, 1914; MS004-122
    - Correspondence with Clark Howell, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, letters, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Testimonies, 1915.; SERIES 2, Subseries 3; 0.6 Linear feet; (2 document cases)
    Subseries 3, Testimonies, contains transcripts of the U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations that took place in Atlanta in March 1915. The hearings, which were closed to the public, were overseen by Alexander Daly. Strike leaders, members of the United Textile Workers union, members of the Men and Religion Forward movement, and strike participants testified for the striking workers. Numerous company officials, including Oscar Elsas and Gordon Johnstone, as well as employees who had remained loyal, workers who did not go on strike or who were unhappy with the strike, and others sympathizing with management testified for the management side.
    The testimonies are arranged in the order in which the individuals appeared at the hearing; the testimonies for the strikers are followed by the testimonies for management.
    - Ware, Minnie B. (M.B.W.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Testimony of Minnie B. Ware, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-001
    - Wilson, Alfred J. (A.J.W.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Nations, Sarah (S.N.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Testimony of Sarah Nations, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-002
    - Pressley, Elizabeth (E.P.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Samuel (S.W.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Medlock, George (G.M.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - McFarland, Lina (L. McF.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Testimony of Lina McFarland, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-004
    - Johnson, Francis (F.J.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Testimony of Francis Johnson, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-005
    - Smith, Mamie Olive, Mrs. (M.O.S.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Odell, Rufus (R.O.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Testimony of Rufus Odell, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-006
    - Marks, Shuford B. (S.B.M.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Testimony of Shuford B. Marks, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-007
    - Marquardt, Louie (L.M.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Testimony of Louie Marquardt, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-008
    - Jackson, Marion M. (M.M.J.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Testimony of Marion M. Jackson, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-009
    - Briley, Lucretia, Mrs. (L.B.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Testimony of Lucretia Briley, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-011
    - Irwin, R.F. (R.F.I.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Testimony of R. F. Irwin, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-010
    - Howell, Columbus (C.L.H.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Buford, G.R., Rev. (G.R.B.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Fleming, W.E. (W.E.F.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Garrett, W.V., Dr. (W.V.G.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Testimony of W. V. Garrett, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-012
    - Chapman, James J. (J.J.C.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Clark, Andrew Jackson (A.J.C.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Testimony of Andrew Jackson Clark, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-013
    - Cruse, Hazel C. (H.C.C.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Mullinax, H. Newbern (H.N.M.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Testimony of H. Newbern Mullinax, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-014
    - Allen, William J. (W.J.A.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Awtry, E. Newton (E.N.A.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Awtry, E.S. (E.S.A.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Hall, James G., Dr. (J.G.H.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Testimony of James G. Hall, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-015
    - Schaffer, William C., Dr. (W.C.S.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Turner, Lee (L.T.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Reagan, T.J. (T.J.R.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Carson, M.A., Mrs. (M.A.C.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Wright, Robert H. (R.H.W.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Testimony of Robert H. Wright, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-016
      - List of witnesses for the defendant and the complainant in the investigation of Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills by the Commission on Industrial Relations, Mary 17-27, 1915; MS004-262
    - Burton, Emma, Miss (E.B.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Testimony of Emma Burton, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-017
    - Wright, Robert H., Mrs. (Mrs. R.H.W.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Clinton, Jennie, Mrs. (J.C.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Testimony of Jennie Clinton, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-018
    - McSwain, Virgin (V.McS.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Guffin, Alfred S. (A.S.G.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Hawkins, E.W., Dr. (E.W.H.), March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Sweatt, W.C. (W.C.S.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Testimony of W. C. Sweatt, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-019
    - Wheeler, Mabel Emma, Miss (M.E.W.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Testimony of Mabel Emma Wheeler, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-020
    - Carter, Fannie, Miss (F.C.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Meikleham, H.P. (H.P.M.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Testimony of H.P. Meikleham, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-021
    - Farrell, D.A. (D.A.F.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Testimony of D.A. Farrell, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-022
    - Florence, T.S. (T.S.F.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Stone, R.E., Dr. (R.R.S.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Johnstone, Gordon A. (G.A.J.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Testimony of Gordon A. Johnstone, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-023
    - Rhodes, Clarence A., Dr. (C.A.J.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Rogers, E.H. (E.H.R.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Testimony of E.H. Rogers, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-024
    - Smith, P.A. (P.A.S.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Testimony of P.A. Smith, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-025
    - Elsas, Oscar (O.E.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Testimony of Oscar Elsas, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-026
    - James, John R. (J.R.J.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Gober, Harris (H.G.), March 1915 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Testimony of Harris Gober, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-027
    - Certificate of deposition, 24 April 1914 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Operative reports, 1913-1922.; SERIES 3; 2.8 Linear feet; (7 document cases)
  Series 3, Operative reports, is comprised of the reports of employees secretly hired by management to monitor the union activities and work habits of mill workers, in the Atlanta mill as well as in other Fulton Bag mills. The reports also contain some correspondence of Louis Elsas (Brooklyn), Dave Elsas (Dallas), and Charles White (St. Louis). The series is divided into 7 subseries.
  The operative reports are arranged chronologically within each subseries. The reports of each individual operative are grouped together.
  - Atlanta mill, 1913-1922.; SERIES 3, Subseries 1; 2.0 Linear feet; (5 document cases)
    Subseries 1, Atlanta, consists of over one hundred folders containing operative reports filed for the Atlanta Fulton Bag mill. About half of these reports are filed by operatives employed during the period of the 1914-1915 strike. These reports cover union meetings and other activities of the strikers as well as working conditions, attitudes toward work, and union activities inside the mill. The remaining folders cover the period after the strike up to the early 1920s. These reflect management's continuing concern with work efficiency, working conditions, and union activities. The subseries also includes correspondence with detective agencies from which operatives were hired, and a folder of police reports.
    - A14-05-OP10: Operative #10, May-June 1914 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Testimony of George Medlock, March 17-27, 1915; MS004-003
      - "Report of Operative A.E.W.", June 1, 1914; MS004-125
      - "Report of Operative J.W.W.", June 1, 1914; MS004-126
      - "Report of Operative J.W.W.", June 4, 1914; MS004-127
      - "Report of Operatives J.W.W. and A.E.W.", June 5, 1914; MS004-128
      - "Report of Operative J.W.W.", June 2, 1914; MS004-129
      - "Report of Operative A.E.W.", June 2, 1914; MS004-130
      - "Report of J.W.W Inspector and A.E.W. no. 10", June 3, 1914; MS004-131
      - "Report of Operatives J.W.W. and A.E.W.", June 9, 1914; MS004-132
      - "Report of Operatives J.W.W. and A.E.W.", June 10, 1914; MS004-133
      - "Report of Operatives J.W.W. and A.E.W.", June 9, 1914; MS004-134
    - A13-10-POLR: Police reports, October 1913- May 1915 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - A14-05-COR: Correspondence (folder 1 of 3), May 1914-August 1918 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to the Railway Audit and Inspection Company, May 15, 1914; MS004-135
      - Letter from H. N. Brown, Railway Audit and Inspection Company, to Oscar Elsas, May 19, 1914; MS004-136
      - Invoice from the Railway Audit and Inspection Company, June 15, 1914; MS004-137
    - A14-05-COR: Correspondence (folder 2 of 3), May 1914-August 1918 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - A14-05-COR: Correspondence (folder 3 of 3), May 1914-August 1918 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - A14-06-OP115: Operative #115 (folder 1 of 5), June-October 1914 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - "Report of Operative #115", June 21, 1914; MS004-138
      - "Report of Operative #115", June 18, 1914; MS004-139
      - "Report of Operative #115", June 20, 1914; MS004-140
      - "Report of Operative #115", June 26, 1914; MS004-141
      - "Report of Operative #115", June 27, 1914; MS004-142
      - "Report of Operative #115", July 4, 1914; MS004-143
    - A14-06-OP115: Operative #115 (folder 2 of 5), June-October 1914 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - "Report of Operative #115", July 24, 1914; MS004-144
    - A14-06-OP115: Operative #115 (folder 3 of 5), June-October 1914 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - "Report of Operative #115", July 28, 1914; MS004-145
      - "Report of Operative #115", August 26, 1914; MS004-146
    - A14-06-OP115: Operative #115 (folder 4 of 5), June-October 1914 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - "Report of Operative #115", September 8, 1914; MS004-147
      - "Report of Operative #115", September 9, 1914; MS004-148
      - "Report of Operative #115", September 17, 1914; MS004-149
      - "Report of Operative #115", September 18, 1914; MS004-150
    - A14-06-OP115: Operative #115 (folder 5 of 5), June-October 1914 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - "Report of Operative #115", October 15, 1914; MS004-151
    - A14-06-OPGJM: Operative G.J.M. (folder 1 of 3), June-August 1914 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - A14-06-OPGJM: Operative G.J.M. (folder 2 of 3), June-August 1914 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - "Report of Operative G.J.M.", July 3, 1914; MS004-153
      - Report of Operative G.J.M., July 15, 1914; MS004-154
      - Report of Operative G.J.M., July 15, 1914; MS004-155
    - A14-06-OPGJM: Operative G.J.M. (folder 3 of 3), June-August 1914 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - A14-06-OPHAH: Operative H.A.H., June 1914 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - "Report of Operative H.A.H.", June 10, 1914; MS004-156
    - A14-06-OPHJD: Operative H.J.D., June 1914 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - "Report of Operative H.J.D.", June 9, 1914; MS004-157
      - "Report of Operative H.J.D.", June 10, 1914; MS004-158
    - A14-07-OP12: Operative #12, July 1914 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - A14-06-OP39: Operative #39, July 1914 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - A14-08-OP15: Operative #15, August 1914 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - A14-08-OP41: Operative #41, August 1914 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - A14-08-OP470: Operative #470 (folder 1 of 2), August 1914 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 1, 1914; MS004-159
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 3, 1914; MS004-160
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 5, 1914; MS004-161
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 12, 1914; MS004-162
    - A14-08-OP470: Operative #470 (folder 2 of 2), August 1914 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 14, 1914; MS004-163
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 19, 1914; MS004-164
      - "Report of Operative #470", August 19, 1914; MS004-165